http://indexcomputer.com/privacy_policy.html

Privacy Policy – Policies & Principles - IndexComputer
"Worlds apart in a world of parts"
Shipping
Need help?
Call 1-800-730-0901
Privacy Policy
hard drive
1.8"
More 1.8" hard drive
2.5"
More 2.5" hard drive
3.5"
More 3.5" hard drive
5.25"
Screen Size
LCD monitor 30"
LCD monitor 24"
LCD monitor 22"
LCD monitor 21"
LCD monitor 20"
LCD monitor 19"
LCD monitor 18"
LCD monitor 17"
LCD monitor 16"
LCD monitor 15"
LCD monitor 14"
LCD monitor 10"
LCD for laptop
23"
LCD for laptop 23
20"
LCD for laptop 20
19"
LCD for laptop 19
18"
LCD for laptop 18
17"
LCD for laptop 17
16"
LCD for laptop 16 WSXGA
LCD for laptop 16 WXGA
LCD for laptop 16
15"
LCD for laptop 15
14"
LCD for laptop 14
13"
LCD for laptop 13
12"
LCD for laptop 12
11"
LCD for laptop 11 WXGA
LCD for laptop 11
10"
LCD for laptop 10
9"
LCD for laptop 9
8"
Vostro memory ram
Index Guarantees:
Certified, tested and guaranteed
30 day guarantee
Easy Return Policy
Same Day shipping
Contact us by Phone:
Closed on national holidays
INTRODUCTION:
Indexcomputer.com is committed to protecting your privacy. The information that you enter while placing an order or registering for our newsletters or promotions is the only information that we collect. We use the information to enhance your shopping experience. We do not distribute your personal information to third parties.
Information We Collect:
IndexComputer.com does not collect personal information from visitors. If you are just browsing, we do not seek personal information about you. If you wish to receive special promotions, our registration form will ask you to provide:
Your name
Your e-mail address
Periodically, we send an IndexComputer.com newsletter to our e-mail list. The newsletter features news about watches, new product offerings and seasonal specials. We do not make our mailing list available to other companies. If you no longer wish to receive any promotional materials, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by using the unsubscribe feature in our email.
When placing an order, you will need to provide the following information:
Your name
Your e-mail address
Your billing and shipping address
Your telephone number
The type of credit card you are using if applicable
Your credit card number and expiration date, or other form of payment
The information is used to process and send your order. We also use the information to contact you if there is a problem with your order. We do not share this information with third parties.
Protection of Your Information:
IndexComputer.com takes every precaution to protect our your information. When you submit sensitive information via our website, your information is protected both online and off-line. IndexComputer.com uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name and address during transactions, to provide a safe, secure shopping environment.
Your Consent to This Policy
By using the IndexComputer.com web site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. Changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so you will always know about the information we collect and how we use it.
Over 120 brands and manufacturers in Index' inventory, amongst which there is:
Index computer Remarketing Inc.
is licensed under a
Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License
Permissions beyond the scope of this license may be available on
terms and conditions on indexcomputer.com
